<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ruanne Bornman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ruanne Bornman</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Typography - Test for features</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&#xA;Heading 1 Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(No comment) When You Have Too Much to Do</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>You have a to-do list that scrolls on for days. You are managing multiple projects, getting lots of email and messages on different messaging systems, managing finances and personal health habits and so much more.&#xA;It all keeps piling up, and it can feel overwhelming.&#xA;How do you keep up with it all? How do you find focus and peace and get stuff accomplished when you have too much on your plate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&#xA;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
